Alina Gabriela Ghetler

Junior Frontend Developer

Landsberger Alle 171D Berlin, 10369 +49(0)17629918767 alina.ghetler@gmail.com

BIO

I have a Bachelor Degree in Accounting but in the last 2 years since moving to Berlin I've discovered the beauty of the software industry by attending meetups on different subjects. This inspired me to re focus my career and work on becoming a software developer.

In order to achieve my goal and understand UX principles, I've worked on test applications for a large number of companies such as EyeEm(app for photos), Memorando and GameDuell(games) Ally(local transport application for mobile), Mimi Hearing.

I've started to learn programming by attending meetups organised by OpenTechSchool and also attending online courses on e-learning platforms like Coursera, Udacity and Code Academy.

Currently I'm eager to become a front-end developer (because I like javascript) and in order to achieve this objective I'm looking for an internship or junior developer opportunity.

SKILLS

Programming Languages - JavaScript,HTML5, CSS, Java, Python Frameworks - JQuery, Bootstrap Tools - git, Pentaho Kettle, SPSS Databases - PostgreSQL

INDEPENDENT PROJECTS

Game of Life - http://bit.ly/2iluB8h

Personal Webpage - https://alinaberlin.github.io

- http://alinaghetler.bitballoon.com/

COURSES & TRAININGS

01/2017 - 04/2017 - Web Developer at Career Foundry

11/2016 - 05/2017 - Full Stack Web Development at Free Code Camp

10/2016 - 02/2016 - Creative Web Development - Javascript at ReDi School for Digital Integration

08/2016 - Introduction to Data Analysis at ReDi School for Digital Integration

03/2016 - HTLM5&CSS on Codecademy

02/2016 - JavaScript Basics on Udacity.com

02/2015 - Programming for everybody (Python) on Coursera

EXPERIENCE

Trend Test GMBH, Berlin Germany - Market Research Interviewer

04/2015 - 12/2016

Pizza Hut, Timisoara Romania - Shift Manager

09/2013 - 10/2013

SC Briela SRL, Botosani Romania - Regional Representative

06/2005 - 09/2013

EDUCATION

Petre Andrei University, Iasi - Economics

2005 - 2009

AWARDS

3rd place at "Free Knowledge Game Jam Berlin 2015", 10/2015

Free Knowledge Game Jam is organised by Wikimedia Deutschland in partnership with the Computerspielemuseum Berlin. The 2-day hackathon is centered around Free Knowledge in game development. In groups you will build a prototype game in 24 hours.

Game Jam is a hackathon where 100 game developers, like coders, artists, sound engineers and designers will form teams to develop a prototype computer game in 24 hours.

1st place at Python Competition for Beginners PyLady Berlin, 04/2015